Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Memorial Design Competition Submissions (digital) 6317/027(d)
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Memorial Design Competition Submissions (digital)
2010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection
Kheel Center
Imperato, Rose
6317/027(d)
8.28 cubic feet
8.3 linear ft.
Records, cd-roms.
9130542
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 28, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 24, 2016
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the submissions for the Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Memorial Design Competition.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6317: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection 6317 MB: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Memorabilia 6317 PUBS: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Publications 6317/001: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Remember the Triangle Fire Coalition Records 6317/001 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Remember the Triangle Fire Coalition Audio-Visual Materials 6317/001 MB: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Remember the Triangle Fire Coalition Memorabilia 6317/002 G: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Maribeth Whitehouse, IS 190 Class Graphics 6317/003: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Richard Strassberg 6317/004 PUBS: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Mark Tennyson Publications 6317/005: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection W4 New Music Booklets 6317/005 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection W4 New Music Audio-Visual Materials 6317/006 G: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection University of Iowa Labor Center Graphics 6317/007 P: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Denise J. Murphy Photographs 6317/008 PUBS: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection International Brotherhood of Teamsters, City Employees Union Local 237 Publications 6317/009: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Grey Art Gallery, New York University 6317/010: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Berkeley City College 6317/010 MB: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Berkeley City College Memorabilia 6317/010 P: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Berkeley City College Photographs 6317/011: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Working Women's History Project 6317/012 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection New York Society for Ethical Culture Audio-Visual Materials 6317/013 P: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Paul Margolis Photographs 6317/014: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection 59E59 Theaters 6317/015: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Anabella Lenzu Pamphlets 6317/015 P: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Anabella Lenzu Photographs 6317/016: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Theater for the New City 6317/016 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Theater for the New City Audio-Visual Materials 6317/017: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Bob Brener 6317/017 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Bob Brener Audio-Visual Materials 6317/018: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Manhattan Choral Ensemble 6317/018 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Manhattan Choral Ensemble Audio-Visual Materials 6317/019: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection West End Synagogue 6317/020 AV: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Judson Memorial Church "From the Fire" Audio-Visual Materials 6317/021: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection New York State Museum Pamphlets 6317/022: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Anna Marie Landolfo Collection of Ephemera 6317/023: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection National Center for the Laity Newsletter 6317/024: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection International Labor Rights Forum Pamphlet 6317/025: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection Kheel Center Collection of Newsclippings
Women clothing workers -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Imprato, Rose; Lefevre, Greg; Andrews, Jennifer; Angers, Mary C.; Arroyo, Andrea; Baker, Garin; Baron, Ron; Bart, Harriet; Benefiel, Joan; Bennett, Chris; Bergmann, Meredith, 1955-; Bonner, Jonathan, 1947-; Calicchia, Giancarlo; Chang, Candy; Chutiwongpeti, Sarawut; Claudio, Dayton; Clausen, Ted; Cooper, Susan; Curtiss, Gareth; DeDecker, Jane; Warnock, Douglas; Delgado, Roberto; Einfinger, Carmen; Eisenbach, Ronit, 1962-; Galindo, Felipe; Glenn, Matt; Goldstein, Daniel; Shin, Kyungmi; Gray, Todd; Greengold, Jane; Harmony, Carol; Hegs, Lajos; Hatcher, Brower, 1942-; Jaffe Werner, Stephanie; Kalian, Lucy K. H.; Kalish, Howard; Lanzilloto, Annie; Bernheim, Peter; Larimer, Amy; Laxman, Eric David; Lolo, Lulu; Luery, Susan; Lung, Carole Frances; Manuel, Jefre; McLaughlin, Michael; Meehan, Howard; Miller, Gail; Poethig, Johanna; Moody, Erica; Poueymirou, Jen; Reese, Gabrielle; Regutti, Carol W.; Reynolds, Shahla; Koryn Rolstad Studios; Salenger Colab, Maria; Sarantitis, Joshua; Scott, Dread; Seeman, John; Shahn, Jonathan; Shifrin, Roy; Snow, Tyson; Taylor, Judy; Tunick, Susan; Tunison, Ron; Weisbeck, Diane; Weisbeck, Mark; Mosko, Martin; Wiener, Joshua; Zhao, Suikang; Zlamay, Brenda; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives; Alison Sky, LLC; Triangle Shirtwaist Company; Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection; Triangle Shirtwaist Company -- Fire, 1911
9130542
- Jennifer Andrews and Greg Lefevre & Collection list, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  DVD-box 2
- Mary C. Angers, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  DVD-box 3
- Andrea Arroyo, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  DVD-box 4
- Garin Baker/Carriage House Art Studios, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  DVD-box 5
- Joan Benefiel, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  DVD-box 8
- Jonathan Bonner, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  DVD-box 11
- Roberto Delgado/Douglas Warnock, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  DVD-bx 20
- Ronit Eisenbach and Matter Practice, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  DVD-box 22
- Felipe Galindo, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  DVD-box 23
- Matt Glenn, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  DVD-box 24
- Mags Harries & Lajos Heder, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  DVD-box 29
- Stephanie Jaffe Werner, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  DVD-box 31
- Lucy K.H. Kalian, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  DVD-box 32, 33, 34, 35
- Howard Kalish, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  DVD-box 36
- Carole Frances Lung, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  DVD-box 43
- Michael McLaughlin, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  DVD-box 45
- Gail Miller, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  DVD-box 47
- Regutti Sculptures/Carol W. Regutti, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  DVD-box 51
- Joshua Sarantitis, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  DVD-box 56
- Dread Scott, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  DVD-box 57
- Roy Shifrin, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  DVD-box 58
- Alison Sky, LLC, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  DVD-box 61
- Tattfoo, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  DVD-box 63
- Ron Tunison, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  DVD-box 66
- Mark and Diane Weisbeck, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  DVD-box 67
- Suikang Zhao, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  DVD-box 69
- Jennifer Andrews and Greg Lefevre, 2010 (Box 2)
  letter in box 1 ff 1
- Mary C. Angers, 2010 (Box 3)
  letter in box 1 ff 2; layout sheets in box 71
- Andrea Arroyo, 2010 (Box 4)
  letter in box 1 ff3
- Garin Baker/Carriage House Art Studio, 2010 (Box 5)
  letter in box 1 ff4
- Ron Baron, 2010 (Box 6)
- Harriet Bart, 2010 (Box 7)
- Joan Benefiel, 2010 (Box 8)
  letter in box 1 ff5
- Chris Bennett, 2010 (Box 9)
- Meredith Bergmann, 2010 (Box 10)
- Jonathan Bonner, 2010 (Box 11)
  letter in box 1 ff6
- Giancarlo Calicchia, 2010 (Box 12)
- Candy Chang, 2010 (Box 13)
- Sarawut Chutiwongpeti, 2010 (Box 14)
- Dayton Claudio, 2010 (Box 15)
- Ted Clausen, 2010 (Box 16)
- Susan Cooper, 2010 (Box 17)
- Gareth Curtiss, 2010 (Box 18)
- Jane DeDecker, 2010 (Box 19)
- Roberto Delgado/Douglas Warnock, 2010 (Box 20)
  letter in box 1 ff7
- Carmen Einfinger, 2010 (Box 21)
- Ronit Eisenbach, 2010 (Box 22)
  letters in box 1 ff8
- Felipe Galindo, 2010 (Box 23)
  letter in box 1 ff9
- Matt Glenn, 2010 (Box 24)
  pamphlet in box 1 ff10
- Daniel Goldstein, 2010 (Box 25)
- Todd Gray, Kyungmi Shin, 2010 (Box 26)
- Jane Greengold, 2010 (Box 27)
- Carol Harmony, 2010 (Box 28)
- Mags Harries & Lajos Heder, 2010 (Box 29)
  letter in box 1 ff11
- Brower Hatcher, 2010 (Box 30)
- Stephanie Jaffe Werner, 2010 (Box 31)
- Lucy K.H. Kalian, 2010 (Box 32)
  letter in box 1 ff13
- Lucy K.H. Kalian (2 of 4), 2010 (Box 33)
- Lucy K.H. Kalian (3 of 4), 2010 (Box 34)
  letter in box 1 ff 13
- Lucy K.H. Kalian (4 of 4), 2010 (Box 35)
  letter in box 1 f13
- Howard Kalish, 2010 (Box 36)
  letter in box 1 ff14
- Annie Lanzilloto and team (1 of 2), 2010 (Box 37)
- Annie Lanzilloto and team (2 of 2), 2010 (Box 38)
- Amy Larimer/Peter Bernheim, 2010 (Box 39)
- Eric David Laxman, 2010 (Box 40)
- Lulu Lolo, 2010 (Box 41)
- Susan Luery, 2010 (Box 42)
- Carol Frances Lung, 2010 (Box 43)
  letter in box 1 ff15
- Jefre Manuel, 2010 (Box 44)
- Michael McLaughlin, 2010 (Box 45)
  letter in box 1 ff16
- Howard Meehan, 2010 (Box 46)
- Gail Miller, 2010 (Box 47)
  letter in box 1 ff17
- Johanna Poethig, 2010 (Box 48)
- Jen Poueymirou and Erica Moody, 2010 (Box 49)
- Gabrielle Reese, 2010 (Box 50)
- Regutti Sculptures/Carol Regutti, 2010 (Box 51)
  letter in box 1 ff18
- Shahla Reynolds (1 of 2), 2010 (Box 52)
- Shahla Reynolds (2 of 2), 2010 (Box 53)
- Koryn Rolstad Studios, 2010 (Box 54)
- Maria Salenger Colar, 2010 (Box 55)
- Joshua Sarantitus, 2010 (Box 56)
  letter in box 1 ff19
- Dread Scott, 2010 (Box 57)
  letter in box 1 ff20
- John Seeman, 2010 (Box 58)
- Jonathan Shahn, 2010 (Box 59)
- Ray Shifrin, 2010 (Box 60)
  letter in box 1 ff21
- Alison Sky, 2010 (Box 61)
  letter in box 1 ff22
- Tyson Snow, 2010 (Box 62)
- Tattfoo, 2010 (Box 63)
  letter in box 1 ff23
- Judy Taylor, 2010 (Box 64)
- Susan Tunick, 2010 (Box 65)
- Ron Tunison, 2010 (Box 66)
  letter in box 1 ff24
- Mark and Diane Weisbeck, 2010 (Box 67)
  letter in box 1 ff25
- Joshua Wiener and Martin Mosko, 2010 (Box 68)
- Suikang Zhao, 2010 (Box 69)
  letter in box 1 ff26
- Brenda Ziamay, 2010 (Box 70)
- Mary Angers - 3 sheets of layouts from the DVD submission, 2010 (Box 71)
  DVD-in box 3; letter in box 1 ff2